Hello? Hi.It's Laura Cariton here.
你好？-你好，我是劳拉·卡瑞顿。
We've just arrived at the holiday flat, but I can't get the hot water and heating to work.
我刚到达假日公寓，但是我不能打开热水和暖气。
Oh right!That's easy.Don't worry.
好的！这很简单，别担心。
In the upstairs cupboard,you'll find the water heater.
在楼上的柜橱里，你会找到热水器。
You'll see three main controls on the left at the bottom of the heater.
你会看到加热器底部的左面有3个主要的控制装置。
The first one - the round one on the far left - is the most important one for the heating and hot water.
第一个，也就是最左边圆形的那个是加热和热水器最重要的控制装置。
It's the main control switch.
这是总控制开关，
Make sure it's in the 'on' position.
确定它位于“开”的位置。
The switch itself doesn't light up, but the little square below will be black if the switch is 'off'.
开关不会变亮，但是如果开关位于“关”的位置，底下的小方块是黑色的。
That's probably what's happened - it's got switched off by mistake.
这可能就是原因，它可能不小心关掉了。
The middle one of these three controls - you'll see it's slightly larger than the first one - controls the radiators.
中间的那个，你可以看到它比第一个大一点，控制着暖气。
If you feel cold while you're there and need the radiators on,this needs to be turned to maximum.
如果你在那里觉得冷，需要开暖气，你要把它开到最大。
The last of the three controls - the one on the right - is usually on about a number four setting which for the water in the taps is usually quite hot enough.
三个控制装置的最后一个，位于右边的那个，通常开到4号档位，这时从水龙头出来的水通常足够热了。
Below the heating controls in the middle is a small round plastic button.
在加热控制装置下面的中间有一个小的圆形塑料按钮。
If there isn't enough water in the pipes,sometimes the heater goes out.
如果管道里没有足够的热水，有时加热器就会熄火。
If this happens you'll need to press this button to reset the heater.
如果出现这种情况，你需要按这个钮重启加热器。
Hold it in for about five seconds and the heater should come on again.
按住大约5秒，加热器就会重新开始。
Then there's a little square indicator under the third knob that's kind of alarm light.
然后，在第三个把手下面的小方形指示器是一种报警灯。
It'll flash if you need to reset the heater.
如果你需要重启加热器，它会闪烁。
It sounds complicated...
听起来很复杂……
I'm sure you won't have any problems with it.
我肯定你不会有问题的。
There should be some more instructions on the side of the heater.
加热器的旁边应该有更多的说明。
Call me back if you can't make it work. Okay.
如果你还弄不了就给我打电话。好的。